[Music]
Microsoft copilot is AI powered
assistant that helps to spark creativity
increase productivity and eliminate T
tasks in this release we continue to add
kilot capabilities to business Central
and in this session we will learn about
capability which helps to deal with one
of the important area of the product
sales documents imagine that you are new
to the role and you need to create sales
document like sales quote invoice or
order and uh your company has a quite
extensive catalog of products and you
need you're not familiar to it yet in
full details so searching for the spe
for the right product might be a
challenging task especially if the key
details are not stored in the item
directly
but present in the product catalog or
for example represented in the item
attributes how would you do that search
and filter another scenario uh is when
you're dealing with a longterm customer
and the approaching for the new business
deal and they suggest to work with one
of the recent successful deals like uh
use it as a starting point the problem
is that customer might not be very clear
about uh what they're referring to is it
like sales invoice or shipment or maybe
it was quot and which exactly document
they mentioned and what is the date I
think copilot will be great help here
let's see sales line suggestion with
copilot in action so this sales line
suggestion feature is available in
multiple sales document including sales
order uh sales scod and sales invoice
for this particular uh demo let's see in
the context of sales code imagine you
have received an email from a customer
uh inquiring about some items so what
you will do you will go to sales
codes create a new sales
code assign the customer for which you
want to create uh this quotation for and
now you can see we have a new action
called Suggest sales line and when you
click this action this new prompt
dialogue is uh open up which basically
uh takes natural language as an input so
you can enter in a way which you are
most comfortable with and there are two
main intents that are supported over
here either you can list the items that
you need with the quantities or you can
refer any existing document that you
want uh the lines to be copied from to
assist you to get started uh we have
something called prompt guides which can
be used as a starting point of for
entering whatever uh prompt that you
want to enter so let's say for the
document lookup we have like St starting
point either you can say copy from any
existing order number or you can say
something like copy from last invoice
similarly when you are listing uh the
items you can just say add items and
list all the items that you need uh with
the quantities and you can refer the
items with any information that you are
already familiar with so let's start
with copy from last inv as the first
example and when I press generate the
copar is smart enough to identify the
intent and it suggests the invoice for
this particular customer so for
reference on the right hand side you can
see the copilot found uh this particular
uh posted sales and voice uh for this
particular uh customer and copy all the
lines from there now you can actually
review these uh lines and uh change the
description or the quantity if you like
uh Delete any lines that you want and
insert so maybe this was not the uh
document or you were actually looking
for so you can actually go back uh using
this edit prompt and you can say
something like copy
from invoice 3196 it's just a number
that I remember on top of my head uh
some invoice that I recall so you can
see just by mentioning 3196 the
co-pirate was smart enough to find a
posted sales invoice with this U invoice
number which is the 3196 was just a
partial
of this document number and then all the
lines from that document were suggested
for reference you can always open that
document and see uh what was actually in
the actual document uh that the lines
were copied from the important thing
over here is like uh you can search not
only on the base of uh document number
but you can also search based on
external reference number or reference
number or few other fields as
well so that was the first uh intent
that you can you like copy from any
existing document so uh let's explore
the second intent which is uh specifying
the items that uh the customer actually
need so what I can do is actually go
back and say something like I
need office
desk and two
blue office chairs and press
generate the co-art would be smart
enough now to say okay you are actually
looking for items these are the
particular items that you are looking
for
and suggest you lines based on
that so here you can see uh we searched
for uh office desk and uh two blue
office chairs so the co-pilot suggested
this aan desk and London chair as the
suggestions for these items but the
question arised like why did goir uh
selected this desk or this particular
chair for example for chair I look for
blue office chair so if I go to the item
itself the one that the copilot
suggested and see the item card and I
can actually see the category of this
item was actually office chair and if I
scroll down over here the attribute the
blue is basically defined as an
attribute for this item so when you
search for a particular item we are not
only looking at the description or the
name of the item we are looking all the
related uh fields and tables for an item
including uh categories attributes uh
translations and Etc since this result
is AI generated so there a room uh that
the result might not be what exactly you
expected so to assist you to review
these result we have something called
UNC confidence that you can ask which is
an extra information about how the
co-pirate feel the results that were
suggested match against your initial Cy
so when I press uh lines and confidence
and press generate it will give me two
piece of extra information the
confidence that the c-y feel this result
match with your uh your initial prompt
and also the search STS that were
actually used to find these items so you
can see for chairs we uh the search St
that were used for office chairs and
blue and in case there are synonyms for
each item the coprite also search for
those as well and now uh there's one
more thing called uh the matching
criteria based on how precise you want
your search to be you you have multiple
options that you can choose for imagine
you have a request from customer who is
not familiar with the items stored in
your system so you can for that
particular case you can either choose
permissive or balance but if you know
your uh system well enough then you can
even go for precise as a matching so we
will make sure all the keywords are uh
existing for a particular items and they
match exactly so now let's take this one
step further imagine you have received
an email from a customer uh which is
like praising you for the few items that
he uh actually bought which was the
black office chair and a conference
table and he basically asking details
about two more uh items that he want to
buy which is black office chair and blue
office desk so what you can do as the
user of this feature you can actually
copy the entire email and paste it
inside the prompt you can copy the email
uh inside the prompt as it is and press
generate so once I press generate the
co-pilot is smart enough to identify
First what was the user intent inside
the email and which were the items that
the user is only referring to and which
were the items that the user is willing
to buy so the co- parate only uh
consider those items and try to search
for those items inside our system I can
review all the lines that were suggested
the items I can see the confidence is
high and I can see all the Search terms
that uh the copy Ed to identify these
items and then I can press
insert so these lines will be inserted
inside the sales code and now all I have
to do is send this code to the customer
back to you Andre to explain and some
more insights about this feature very
impressive uh that looks like future is
here or almost here of course we know uh
it's not magic it's technology and each
technology probably requires some uh
details to be discovered let's look into
the into the details first of all when
we we're exploring search of the product
which fields and which tables system use
so we know about item attributes and
catalog already from the demo uh but
also we can see item reference variant
transaction translations and extended
text lines are also taken into the
account what is not taken into the
account at this version is the marketing
text or any
attachments when we dealing with a
search for the document we search for
four documents we search for the
existing sales quotes and orders or for
the posted shipments and the posted
invoices and we look for different
fields which may contain the number
either internal ones or external
ones we also use document date as a as a
main date and we also use it for uh to
identify the last or for the
Sorting all right so this is about
data I would like to remind that this
data is your data and uh it's not used
it's not used to train any compilot
capabilities and your data is very much
protected
by comprehensive Enterprise compliance
and security controls all right and if
you would't like to know more uh about
responsible AI uh standards by Microsoft
you can always find them in the
Microsoft website search for responsible
AI standards and you will see how to
ensure fairness reliability and safety
and inclusiveness and transparency and
accountability all right about this
specific capability of the co-pilot it
will be available in the business
Central online also known as a software
as a service so the cloud version it
will be available with the 2024 release
Wave 1 which is starting in April
starting from the US regions it will be
available in in almost all regions
except Canada and I will explain why
because the this capability first
available in the preview in the English
and different type of English language
Australian or New Zealand or or British
ones but not in other languages and in
Canada it's a legal requirement to
release software in both languages in
English and in French so that's why uh
we cannot make it available in Canada
yet
also uh would like to highlight that
this capability currently uh is at no
additional cost if you have a business
center license you can use co-pilot
capabilities in the
product what if you cannot find
it uh starting point is please find the
co-pilot ni capabilities page where you
can see this uh sales line suggestion
capability in the preview section
together with the other features which
are available and make sure that it is
active it might happen that your
business Central and or Azure open AI
service are located in the different
countries or privacy or compliance
boundaries in this case your
administrator needs to activate the
cross region data transfer then your
business Central can
contact Azure open AI service and and
and use co-pilot what are the
limitations you better to be aware about
so as I mentioned it is in English and
it means that we test it and we know
that it works in the English best other
languages it might work you can you're
free to try it but it's not guaranteed
that it will give you a best result
possible result might be worser
comparing to English
ones also it's very important on how
your data looks like so if you use very
cryptic or uh difficult to understand
for human names and abbreviations in
your product descriptions it will be
also difficult for compilot to deal with
them so you might need to invest some
time into making sure that your product
are represented correctly then copilot
can can find them and understand what it
is also if you happen to operate uh in
Industry which and uh which results that
your product catalog might be specified
as one of the sensitive
topics then you might not get any output
at all now a little bit more about
output uh produced by sales line
suggestion you saw that this is
represent a sales line or very similar
to it and if you're familiar to business
Central there are multiple columns in
the real sales line uh table but at this
point C pilot Works only uh with item
number and Quant
and it only deals with lines of type
item so general ledger resources or
comment lines will be ignored also uh
system will not populate any other
fields in the sales lines it will be
either inherited from the from the
header for example we can talk about
location or shipment date but uh or from
the item itself then system will use a
standard price calculation mechanism to
Define price discount and uh also uh
unit of measure to
use you might also try to combine or
produce some uh some prompts and they
might not be supported for example if
you want to use both product search and
document search that is not implemented
so for example you cannot ask a compiler
to return only specific group of product
from the sales from the posted sales
invoice you will receive all lines of
type item
you also cannot use a specific Customer
because right now kilot will use
customer defined in the document
header when searching for the document
also when you search for product you
need to focus on the product
characteristic product description Etc
but you cannot do like relative ones for
example give me best one or give me the
one which fits to another or sold
together or most sold that one will not
will not return you any any good
results uh also you cannot use prompt
for to do adjustment of the line so like
you cannot modify or decide that you
want some products from specific
locations so location will be inherited
from the header or from the product
itself depends on the setup or you can
specify that and give some discount
again discount will be calculated
automatically
all right now you know uh about uh uh
compilot capability which helps you to
deal with sales lines and
uh thank you for for listening also I
would like to mention that we have other
sessions with other compilot
capabilities being available
uh feel free to watch them as well and
uh thank you for watching
enjoy business Central